I just know that there's a lot of y'all out there who are like, yeah, like I was raised up, not
dragged up. Have you watched Side Effects of Integrity? That's the latest episode of Small
Doses Podcast. This episode is for you. I feel like so many people are very like, yeah, why can't
you just do that for that? Like, what's the big deal? Why is it such a thing? Like, what are you
even like protecting for? If you're somebody that is in a business, if you're somebody that's trying
to get a career, if you're somebody that's a climber, that's an ambitious person, you need
to listen to this episode because I want you to check out what me and Melanie Fiona are talking
about as it relates to the fact that your climb might be a little longer if you're carrying
your integrity on your back. You can check out the new episode of Small Doses Side Effects of
Integrity with Melanie Fiona wherever you get your podcasts, and it is now live on YouTube
at AmandaSealsTV. Tell a friend, like, subscribe, all that good stuff.